{
    "question": "1. Ryan    : Can you tell me how to get to the nearest restaurant?\r\nHani\r\nmay be you can ask the policeman over there.\r\nYes, there is one across the street\r\nNext to library\r\nBehind the hotel\r\nI'm sorry. I don't live here.\r\nE. Yap, just go straight\r\n\u062a\u06cc\u0646 \u062f\u0646\r\n2. Siska : Can you tell me where Doni's house is?\r\nGrace : Just go along Mulawarman street.\r\nFrom the dialogue we know that ......\r\nA. Grace knows where Doni's house is\r\nB. They will go to Doni's house\r\n\u0421.\r\nSiska knows where Doni's house\r\nGrace doesn't know where Doni's house\r\nSiska and Grace talking about Mulawarman street\r\n\u0646\u062f\u0627\u062f\u0646 \u0648\u200b",
    "attachments": [],
    "answers": [
        {
            "answer": "<p>Jawaban:</p><p>2. A. Grace knows where Doni&#039;s house is</p><p></p><p></p><p>Penjelasan:</p><p>hope you find this helpful^\u2022^</p><p></p>",
            "attachments": []
        }
    ],
    "related_questions": [
        {
            "slug": "whabere-wiwthe-not-compton-canadener-piracy-is-a-crime-where-529",
            "question": "Whabere?    #wiwthe not compton ?\r\ncanadener\r\nPiracy is a crime\r\nWhere do you probably find me Now?\r\n10 The notre above means that\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><u><em><strong>MAKSUDNYA ARTI YA ???</strong></em></u></p><p><u><em><strong>ARTI NYA :</strong></em></u></p><p></p><p></p><p><strong>apa?</strong></p><p><strong>#wiwthe bukan compton ?</strong></p><p><strong>canadener</strong></p><p><strong>Pembajakan adalah kejahatan</strong></p><p><strong>Di mana Anda mungkin menemukan saya Sekarang?</strong></p><p><strong>10 Notre di atas artinya </strong></p><p><strong></strong></p><p><strong></strong></p><h2>MAAF KALO SALAH SEMOGA MEMBANTU :D</h2>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "susi-dan-susan-pergi-ke-singapura-738",
            "question": "Susi dan susan pergi ke Singapura\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>Susi and Susan goes to Singapore </p>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>cakep</p><p></p><p>#sombongamat...</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "the-text-is-for-no-3-5-i-have-a-little-sister-her-name-is-sals-915",
            "question": "The text is for no 3 - 5    I have a little sister. Her name is Salsa She is only a year old. She is cute. Salsa like a boy\r\nbecause her hair is very short. She can walk but she can't speak. She likes walking around\r\nthe house\r\nSalsa likes to play ball. Mother gave her a ball yesterday. The ball is soft Salsa likes to kick\r\nthe ball I love my sister very much. She has the best smile in the world\r\n3. Who is Salsa\r\na. The writer's baby\r\nb. The writer's little brother\r\nc. The writer's little sister\r\nd. The writer's little boy \u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>C.The writers little sister</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "3-one-day-when-the-people-assigned-to-collect-tribute-to-aji-ta-679",
            "question": "3. One day, when the people assigned to collect    tribute to Aji Tatin were riding the boat\r\nThe underlined word above has the same\r\nmeaning with ....\r\na\r\npayment\r\nd. appraisal\r\nb. praise\r\nachievment\r\nhatred\r\ne.\r\nC.\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><u><em><strong></strong></em></u></p><p><u><em><strong>MAKSUDNYA ARTI YA ???</strong></em></u></p><p><u><em><strong></strong></em></u></p><p><u><em><strong>ARTINYA :</strong></em></u></p><p><u><em><strong></strong></em></u></p><p><u><em><strong>3. Suatu hari, ketika orang-orang yang ditugaskan untuk mengumpulkan</strong></em></u></p><p><u><em><strong>penghormatan kepada Aji Tatin sedang naik perahu</strong></em></u></p><p><u><em><strong>Kata yang digarisbawahi di atas memiliki kesamaan</strong></em></u></p><p><u><em><strong>artinya dengan ....</strong></em></u></p><p><u><em><strong>Sebuah</strong></em></u></p><p><u><em><strong>pembayaran</strong></em></u></p><p><u><em><strong>d. penilaian</strong></em></u></p><p><u><em><strong>b. memuji</strong></em></u></p><p><u><em><strong>prestasi</strong></em></u></p><p><u><em><strong>kebencian</strong></em></u></p><p><u><em><strong>e.</strong></em></u></p><p><u><em><strong>C. </strong></em></u></p><p><u><em><strong></strong></em></u></p><h2><u><em><strong></strong></em></u></h2><p><u><em><strong></strong></em></u></p><p><u><em><strong></strong></em></u></p><h2>MAAF KALO SALAH SEMOGA MEMBANTU :D</h2><p><u><em><strong></strong></em></u></p><p><u><em><strong></strong></em></u></p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "ithank-youopen-your-dictionary-if-you-want-to-know-the-me-412",
            "question": "I,thank you.......open your dictionary if you want to know the meaning of the words easily    tolong bantu jawab\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban: can</strong></p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>harusnya think . thank nya typo tuh</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "when-will-doni-hold-his-party-265",
            "question": "When Will Doni hold his party",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>saya orang indonesi </p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>saya belajar tertip</p><p></p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "7-aga-vino-can-you-help-me-fix-my-computer-vino-id-love-to-907",
            "question": "7. AGA : Vino, can you help me fix my computer?    VINO: I'd love to, but today my schedule is full. What about tomorrow?\r\nFrom the conversation, we know that ...\r\nA. Vino cannot help Aga.\r\nC. Vino refuses to help Aga.\r\nB. Vino will fix Aga's computer today D. Vino will fix Aga's computer tomorrow\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>Jawabannya adalah D. Vino will fix Aga&#039;s computer tomorrow</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "<p>Jawaban:</p><p>D. Vino will fix Aga&#039;s coputer tomorrow</p><p></p><p>Thanyou &lt;3</p><p></p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "salah-satu-permainan-tradisional-780",
            "question": "Salah satu permainan tradisional\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>egrang, congklak</p><p></p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>semoga membantu</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>petak umpet,bola bekel, gundu,tali karet</p><p></p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "simple-present-formula-subject-to-be-am-is-are-verbl-676",
            "question": "Simple Present Formula    (+) Subject + to be (am, is, are) + verbl+o/e\r\n- Subject + to be (am, is, are) + pot+verbl+ole\r\n(?) To be (am, is, are) + subject tverbl+o/c\r\nComplete the sentences below with (+), (-) and (?) by looking at the formula above\r\n6. (-) Linda is not a teacher\r\n(Score 15)\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>(+) Linda is a teacher</p><p>(?) is Linda a teacher?</p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>I hope it can help u, </p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "3-ms-gina-have-you-taken-your-lunch-sandy-ms-gina-well-l-857",
            "question": "3. Ms. Gina : Have you taken your lunch?\r\nSandy\r\nMs. Gina : Well, let's go find some meals.\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>3. Ms. Gina : Have you taken your lunch?\n</p><p>Sandy: <strong>No, I have not.</strong>\n</p><p>Ms. Gina : Well, let&#039;s go find some meals.\u200b</p><p></p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>Pertanyaan dari Ms.Gina menggunakan bentuk Present Perfect Tense karena dia bertanya apakah Sandy sudah makan atau belum. Maka jawaban sesuai dengan kalimat yang dicetak tebal, yaitu memberitahukan bahwa Sandy belum makan, karenanya, Ms.Gina mengajak Sandy untuk mencari makanan bersama.</p><p>Semoga membantu ya.</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}